Search the pictures.
Check out different search results.
Does it seem as if it is stated?
The last one might not be relevant.
The eyes should go to the most important thing: the sender.
Who is talking?
What is the site?
Use quotation marks when searching.
Then you only get the wording.
You can delineate names, places and phrases that you want to search for.
If you suspect that something is fake, try using it.
For example...
... "Elisa Granato" and then the word fake.
Then you get this.
You can also click around the site.
Write "Click around the site".
Try it.
Then it may turn out who is behind it.
It is a bit difficult to determine who is behind this site.
And when I made my illustration of how rumors spread ...
So nice!
Some circles.
We're talking about four events-
-But something that has been noticed so that so many people have heard about it.
Very good!
I am so impressed with you!
But what should you do now?
Now?
This will roll on.
We are out of for life here.
-Money in the bank!
-We shall see...
-The producer!
-The job offers!
Social distancing!
- Edwin, I received your email about the program idea.
GREATE!
You are fully trained regarding source criticism.
And you have such a ... young speech.
Should we go and talk about the program?